Hilda Mason, City Council 029
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - DC of Columbia FY 1998 Budget and Financial Plan (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Global Focus a new Foreign Policy Agenda, 1997 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Tiennial Assessment Process, 1997 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Policy Fax '97, 1997 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Education and Cultural Institutions 1 of 2, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Education and Cultural Institutions 2 of 2, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - C-Span - 1997 U.S Congressional Directory (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - FY 1998 DC Budget and Financial Plan Legislative Package, 1997 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - DC Proposed D.C Procurement Regulations 1 of 2, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - DC Proposed D.C Procurement Regulations 2 of 2, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Enterprise Funds 1 of 2, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Enterprise Funds 1 of 2, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Other Agencies/ Departments, 1997 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Mayors Transmittal Letter, 1997 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Capital Improvement Plan and FY 1998 Capital Budget 1 of 2 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Capital Improvement Plan and FY 1998 Capital Budget 2 of 2 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Changing Population in the District and "Index it", 1991 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Commissioner Connection and USC Policy Brief, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - FY 1998 - FY 2003 DC Capital Improvement Plan and FY 1998 Capital Budget 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - FY 1998 - FY 2003 DC Capital Improvement Plan and FY 1998 Capital Budget 2 of 2, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Magnificent Failure: The Maryland Constitutional Convention of 1967-1968, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - With an Understanding Heart: Constitutional Making in Hawaii, 1971 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Revision Success: The Sixth Illinois Constitutional Convention, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Constitutional Making in Missouri: The Convention of 1943-1944, 1971 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Alaska's Constitutional Convention, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Alaska's Constitutional Convention, 1975 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Rhodes Tavern (Preservation and Restoration, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Oversight Hearing and Markup Subcom. On Metro Affairs, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Home rule for DC Background and Legislative History, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Home rule for DC Background and Legislative History, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Hearings Before Subcommittee on the Constitution of Ctte. On Jud., 1978 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Omnibus Reconciliation Act 1981 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Hearings and Markup of Subcom. On Gov't Affairs and Budget, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Omnibus Reconciliation Act 1981 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Omnibus Reconciliation Act 1981 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - 21st Grantee Performance Report for the Community Development Block Grant Program, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - DC Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Authority, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - President's National Capital Revitalization and Self Government Improvement Plan, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Letter to Dr. Andrew Brimmer Regarding the Authority's Strategic Plan, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - FY 1995- FY 1999 Multi Year Plan Restructuring the Future, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Comprehensive Annual Financial Report, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - DC Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Authority, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - DC Public Library Public Hearing before D.C Ed and Lib, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - FY 1996 Operating Budget Requirements (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Board of Ed. Budget - 1996 Transmittal, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Report on "the necessity and costs of District of Columbia services", 1997 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - The Federal payment to the District of Columbia 1790-1980, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - DC of Columbia Appropriations Bill - 1997 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Capital Funds Improvement funds report, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - DC Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Authority, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - DC Comprehensive Annual Financial Report, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Board of Education's Recommended FY 1996 Operating Budget, 1994 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Summary Status Report 1 of 2, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Summary Status Report 2 of 2, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - How to Understand Local Gov't Financial Statements, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Arthur Anderson Audit Committees in 1990s, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - An Elected Officials Guide to Guide to fund Balance, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Audit Management Handbook, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - 1994 Annual Audit Briefing (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Comprehensive Annual Financial Report, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Arthur Anderson Global Best Practices for Audit Committees, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - 1995 DC Audit Briefing 1 of 2 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - 1995 DC Audit Briefing 2 of 2 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Mets Project Overview for the D.C Financial Authority, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Statehood - 1987 Convention Res'n, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Statehood Admission and Statehood Literature, 1975-1995 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Library of Congressional Research Service, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Statehood Economic Testimony Brimmer et. Al, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Statehood Party Convention April 11 1987 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Statehood Testimony March 30 1987 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Hilda Mason Statehood Party AD, undated (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Statehood Congressional Testimony, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Hearing and Markups Subcom. On Jud Manpower and Ed., 1979 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Josephine Butler, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Statehood Constitution, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Statehood Financial Records, 1985-1986 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Statehood Misc., 1979-1989 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Statehood Filing, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - United States Court of Appeals for the DC Circuit, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Paul Robeson Campaign for Racial Ethnic Harmony, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - The Common Denominator June 29 1998 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Ballot of Bust, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence on District's Colonial Status, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Voting Rights Petition, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - The New Case for D.C Voting Rights?, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - in the United States District for the District of Columbia, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - The Briefing Book for D.C Statehood Bill, undated (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Twenty Citizens of DC vs William Jefferson Clinton, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Statehood for the New Columbia, 1993 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - FY 1980 Budget for D.C Public Schools, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Sumner School, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - H.R 51 Statehood Bill/Constitution/Stickers/Buttons, 1982-1989 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Statehood Filing 2 of 2, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Special Education, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Quality Education Correspondence, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - H.R 6271 and De Register Documents, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Sumner School building and repair 1 of 2, 1980-1981 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Sumner School building and repair 2 of 2, 1980-1981 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Authority of the Mayor to Respond to Review Shortfall in FY 1980 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Utility Sales between Utilities at Lower rate, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - D.C Board of Elections, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Supreme Court University of California v Bakke, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Vacant District owned Buildings, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - DC Government Comprehensive Merit Personnel Act of 1978 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - General Election November 4 1980 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Renaldo L. Spivey v Marion Barry, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Board of Education Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - DC Self Government Reorganization Act of 1973 (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - 79 Rapid Transit Conference, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - Comparative Cost of Two Voting Systems - FY 79-FY 89, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - H.R 12116 Bill, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 22)
  - Voting - Ballot Sample - FAQ Voting System, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 23)
  - Washington Post Article Budget Correspondence, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - DC Statehood Party Registration 10-21-78, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 25)
  - The 95th Congress Major Legislation, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 26)
  - Master File D.C Board of Elections, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 27)
  - 3-15-91 Jousting over the School Budget, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 28)
  - H.R 12116 an Act and 5.2316 a Bill, 1977-1978 (Box 109, Folder 29)
  - Second Supplemental FY 1980 Budget, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 30)
  - Rehabilitation of the Sumner School Building, 1982 (Box 109, Folder 31)
  - In Consideration of a policy on school closing and building disposition, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 32)
  - John Edward Guianan v Board of Elections and Ethics, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 33)
  - Statement at Large Council member Betty Ann Kane on Budget Process, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 34)
  - Merit Personnel Act of 1978 (Box 109, Folder 35)
  - Therman E. Evans v Halter E. Washington, 1976 (Box 109, Folder 36)
  - DC Court of Appeals Marion Barry v Nate Bush, 1990 (Box 109, Folder 37)
  - Schedule 1 DC Service Schedule, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 38)
  - Welfare/Health care/budget articles, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 39)
  - Sumner School from Rieffel to Lockridge and Reed, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 40)
  - John Edward Guianan v Board of Elections and Ethics of DC, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 41)
  - Statehood Constitutional Convention, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 42)
  - Constitution of the State of New Columbia, 1982 (Box 109, Folder 43)
  - Sumner School Correspondence, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 44)
  - D.C Statehood Constitutional Convention Rules and Calendar, 1982 (Box 109, Folder 45)
  - Artist in Residence and seminar presentations on Black - Classical keyboard composers: Ruth Norman, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 46)
  - Healthy babies project, 1996 (Box 109, Folder 47)
  - TB News Publication, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 48)
  - The Orphaned Capital Article, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 49)
  - Washingtoniana Educational Review Issues 1 of 6, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 50)
  - Washingtoniana Educational Review Issues 2 of 6, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 51)
  - Washingtoniana Educational Review Issues 3 of 6, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 52)
  - Washingtoniana Educational Review Issues 4 of 6, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Washingtoniana Educational Review Issues 5 of 6, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Washingtoniana Educational Review Issues 6 of 6, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Articles Misc., 1997 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Articles Misc., 1997 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Chronology History of District of Columbia Public Library, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Keynotes 5, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1995-1997 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1995-1997 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Articles, 1985-1994 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Council Appointments to UDC Board of Trustees Nominating Committee, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Regarding Dannette D. James, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Land Value Capture Correspondence, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Parental Involvement Legislation Correspondence, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Lola Louise Johnson, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Carowitz Nomination, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Congratulations Correspondence, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - WMATA Proposal, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Letter of Recommendation for Barbara Jackson, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - National Capital Planning Commission Mail list Info, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Intro of Ceremonial Resolution to Recognize UDC Honda Varsity Team, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - Community Events/Parks and Rec Correspondence, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 23)
  - Smothers School Receipt Copy, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 23)
  - Access Housing Corporation Proposal, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 25)
  - Condolences form Hilda and Charlie to Jack Evans, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 26)
  - WPGF Annual Luncheon, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 27)
  - Fisher Interim President, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 28)
  - Appointment of Miles Mark Fischer as Distinguished Professor, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 29)
  - Self Reporting Bi Monthly Leave Record, 1992 (Box 110, Folder 30)
  - DC Time and Attendance Street and Summer Contract, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 31)
  - Stanley Correspondence - distinguished professorship, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 33)
  - America the Beautiful Tour, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence Misc., 1994 (Box 110, Folder 35)
  - Project Harvest, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 36)
  - Lorton Prison College Program, undated (Box 110, Folder 37)
  - Founding of Republic of China Correspondence, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 38)
  - DTC Career Institute Complaint, undated (Box 110, Folder 39)
  - Clement Mills Request for Assistance, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 40)
  - Reinstatement Request-Zungu, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 41)
  - Thank you letter to Leaford Williams, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 42)
  - School Space and VHS Recorder Request and Program Suspension, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 43)
  - Letter of Sup. Of Schools for Hearing, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 44)
  - Provost Correspondence, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Jeffery S. Gold Smoking Correspondence, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Pending Property tax legislation, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - WMATA Procurement of Parking Fee Collection Services, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Oct. 29 1993 Correspondence (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Check Copies, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Fenwick Correspondence, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - John. G Stone Correspondence, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Comprehensive School Health Program and Violence at School, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Brooks Correspondence/Superintendent of Schools, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - 34th Anniversary of the African Heritage Dancers and Drummers, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Lester M. Cuffie Appointment Correspondence, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - School transfers based on safety correspondence, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Whitman - Walker Clinic Correspondence, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Television influence on children correspondence and family values, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - In recognition of Marion S. Barry, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - United House of Prayer Marshall Heights Correspondence, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Substance Abuse Program, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - WMATA Road Donation and Metrorail Access, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Condolences to Hilda Mason after sisters death, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Transcript request correspondence, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - Recommendation to phase out DC School of Law, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - Appreciation checks and contributions, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 24)
  - Misc. correspondence, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 25)
  - Mail Log: Thursday Jan.2 1992 (Box 111, Folder 26)
  - Third Annual Candlelight Serenade for the benefit of Rachel's women's center, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 27)
  - Agendas and Mail list 1 of 4, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 28)
  - Agendas and Mail list 2 of 4, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 29)
  - Agendas and Mail list 3 of 4, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 30)
  - Agendas and Mail list 4 of 4, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 31)
  - Agendas and Mail list 1 of 4, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Agendas and Mail list 2 of 4, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Agendas and Mail list 3 of 4, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Agendas and Mail list 4 of 4, 1991 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Appointments - 1992 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Appointments - 1993 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Appointments - 1994 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Appointments - 1979 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Appointments - 1982 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Appointments - 1981 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Appointments - 1980 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - National Appointments, undated (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Appointments - 1984 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Appointments - 1985 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Appointments - 1987 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Appointments - 1986 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Appointments - 1990 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Appointments - 1991 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Appointments - 1988 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Appointments - 1989 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - DC Employees' One Fund Drive, 1993 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Education and Libraries Regular Meeting 4/19/93 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Education and Libraries Regular Meeting 1/11/93, 1993 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Feb. 3 1992. (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Education and Libraries Regular Meeting 5/4/92, 1992 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 4/13/92, 1992 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 9/8/92, 1992 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Education and Libraries Public Offsight Hearing 6/8/92, 1992 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 6/19/92 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Nov. 4 1991 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday November 15 1991 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Oct 21 1991 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Oct. 7 1991 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Oct. 28 1991 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Nov. 4 1991 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday 11/18/91, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Education and Libraries 11/18/91, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 5/16/94, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 5/16/94, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 11/13/93, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Education and Libraries Emergency Meeting 10/5/93, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 10/4/93, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Education and Libraries budget markup 3/11/94, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Mar. 5 1991 1 of 2 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Mar. 5 1991 1 of 2 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 12/13/93, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 12/13/93, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Education and Libraries Roundtable 9/27/93, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Bill 10-272 Board of Trustees of UDC Term holdover Act of 1993 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Bill 10-148 "Confirmation Amendment Act of 1993" (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Apr. 22 1993 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday Jul 8 1991 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries 9/16/91, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Public Hearing Sep. 16 1991 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries July 10 1991 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Education and Libraries Budget Public Hearing 2/10/92, 1992 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Education and Libraries Joint Committee Meeting and Briefing 2/1/93, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 10/18/93, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 4/5/93, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Education and Libraries Rescheduled Regular Meeting 10/21/93, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Education and Libraries Monday May 23 1994 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable and Additional Meeting 6/27/94, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 6/13/94, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 6/06/94, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable and Additional Meeting 6/16/94, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 4/18/94, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Education and Libraries Regular Meeting 5/15/95, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Education and Libraries Additional Committee Meeting 1/13/95, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 9/19/94 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 9/19/94 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Education and Libraries Public Roundtable 1/7/94, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Committee Action UDC Amendment Act of 1993 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Recommendation for Improving Trustee Selection in Public Colleges and Universities, undated (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Membership Central State Coordinating and/or governing boards and public institutional and multicampus governing boards, undated (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Frank Shaffer - Corona Correspondence, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Bill 10-468 Reorganization of Trustees Membership on the Board of Trustees of UDC Amendment Act of 1993 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1993 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Education and Libraries Committee Emergency Meeting 5/26/96, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Education and Libraries Committee Special Meeting 10/3/96, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Education and Libraries Public Oversight Hearing, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Education and Libraries Budget Public Hearing 2/20/92, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Education and Libraries Committee Special Meeting 5/30/96, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Education and Libraries Committee Budget Hearing 5/20/96, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Education and Libraries Committee Public Hearing 4/15/96, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Education and Libraries Committee Public Hearing 9/25/96, 1996 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Boarder babies and Drug Affected Children in the District of Columbia, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - 1994 Budget Request 1 of 2 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - 1994 Budget Request 2 of 2 (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - District of Columbia Armory Board: Response to the Public Services February - 1993 (Box 118, Folder 25)